var en_targets = [
    {
        "Subject":"The salesman",
        "Verb":"traveled",
        "PP1":"to the city",
        "PP2":"for the conference",
        "Math":"98 + 11 = ?",
        "Answer1":109,
        "Answer2":118,
        "Prep1":"to",
        "Prep2":"for",
        "Transitivity":"intransitive",
        "ModifierPosition":"none",
        "ModifierLen":"none",
        "Condition":"short_short",
        "Group":1,
        "Item":1,
        "Filler":"no",
        "Repeat":null,
        "math_question":"14 + 15 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":29
    },
    {
        "Subject":"The salesman",
        "Verb":"traveled",
        "PP1":"to the very popular\ncity",
        "PP2":"for the conference",
        "Math":"5 + 9 = ?",
        "Answer1":14,
        "Answer2":3,
        "Prep1":"to",
        "Prep2":"for",
        "Transitivity":"intransitive",
        "ModifierPosition":"prenominal",
        "ModifierLen":"short",
        "Condition":"long_short",
        "Group":1,
        "Item":2,
        "Filler":"no",
        "Repeat":null,
        "math_question":"5 + 13 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":18
    },
    {
        "Subject":"The salesman",
        "Verb":"traveled",
        "PP1":"to the city",
        "PP2":"for the very popular\nconference",
        "Math":"23 + 44 = ?",
        "Answer1":67,
        "Answer2":77,
        "Prep1":"to",
        "Prep2":"for",
        "Transitivity":"intransitive",
        "ModifierPosition":"prenominal",
        "ModifierLen":"short",
        "Condition":"short_long",
        "Group":1,
        "Item":3,
        "Filler":"no",
        "Repeat":null,
        "math_question":"10 + 10 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":20
    },
    {
        "Subject":"The CEO",
        "Verb":"met",
        "PP1":"with some investors",
        "PP2":"about the product",
        "Math":"86 + 14 = ?",
        "Answer1":100,
        "Answer2":110,
        "Prep1":"with",
        "Prep2":"about",
        "Transitivity":"intransitive",
        "ModifierPosition":"none",
        "ModifierLen":"none",
        "Condition":"short_short",
        "Group":2,
        "Item":1,
        "Filler":"no",
        "Repeat":null,
        "math_question":"13 + 6 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":19
    },
    {
        "Subject":"The CEO",
        "Verb":"met",
        "PP1":"with some very\ninteresting\ninvestors",
        "PP2":"about the product",
        "Math":"8 + 9 = ?",
        "Answer1":17,
        "Answer2":16,
        "Prep1":"with",
        "Prep2":"about",
        "Transitivity":"intransitive",
        "ModifierPosition":"prenominal",
        "ModifierLen":"short",
        "Condition":"long_short",
        "Group":2,
        "Item":2,
        "Filler":"no",
        "Repeat":null,
        "math_question":"8 + 8 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":16
    },
    {
        "Subject":"The CEO",
        "Verb":"met",
        "PP1":"with some investors",
        "PP2":"about the very\ninteresting product",
        "Math":"81 + 93 = ?",
        "Answer1":174,
        "Answer2":164,
        "Prep1":"with",
        "Prep2":"about",
        "Transitivity":"intransitive",
        "ModifierPosition":"prenominal",
        "ModifierLen":"short",
        "Condition":"short_long",
        "Group":2,
        "Item":3,
        "Filler":"no",
        "Repeat":null,
        "math_question":"15 + 10 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":25
    },
    {
        "Subject":"The mother",
        "Verb":"spoke",
        "PP1":"to the principal",
        "PP2":"about her son",
        "Math":"5 + 58 = ?",
        "Answer1":63,
        "Answer2":62,
        "Prep1":"to",
        "Prep2":"about",
        "Transitivity":"intransitive",
        "ModifierPosition":"none",
        "ModifierLen":"none",
        "Condition":"short_short",
        "Group":3,
        "Item":1,
        "Filler":"no",
        "Repeat":null,
        "math_question":"6 + 15 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":21
    },
    {
        "Subject":"The mother",
        "Verb":"spoke",
        "PP1":"to the principal who\nis overworked",
        "PP2":"about her son",
        "Math":"33 + 27 = ?",
        "Answer1":60,
        "Answer2":66,
        "Prep1":"to",
        "Prep2":"about",
        "Transitivity":"intransitive",
        "ModifierPosition":"postnominal",
        "ModifierLen":"short",
        "Condition":"long_short",
        "Group":3,
        "Item":2,
        "Filler":"no",
        "Repeat":null,
        "math_question":"14 + 12 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":26
    },
    {
        "Subject":"The mother",
        "Verb":"spoke",
        "PP1":"to the principal",
        "PP2":"about her son who is\noverworked",
        "Math":"95 + 28 = ?",
        "Answer1":123,
        "Answer2":133,
        "Prep1":"to",
        "Prep2":"about",
        "Transitivity":"intransitive",
        "ModifierPosition":"postnominal",
        "ModifierLen":"short",
        "Condition":"short_long",
        "Group":3,
        "Item":3,
        "Filler":"no",
        "Repeat":null,
        "math_question":"10 + 9 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":19
    },
    {
        "Subject":"The businessman",
        "Verb":"called",
        "PP1":"from the airport",
        "PP2":"about the meeting",
        "Math":"10 + 32 = ?",
        "Answer1":42,
        "Answer2":40,
        "Prep1":"from",
        "Prep2":"about",
        "Transitivity":"intransitive",
        "ModifierPosition":"none",
        "ModifierLen":"none",
        "Condition":"short_short",
        "Group":4,
        "Item":1,
        "Filler":"no",
        "Repeat":null,
        "math_question":"13 + 7 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":20
    },
    {
        "Subject":"The businessman",
        "Verb":"called",
        "PP1":"from the airport\nthat was busy",
        "PP2":"about the meeting",
        "Math":"8 + 82 = ?",
        "Answer1":90,
        "Answer2":92,
        "Prep1":"from",
        "Prep2":"about",
        "Transitivity":"intransitive",
        "ModifierPosition":"postnominal",
        "ModifierLen":"short",
        "Condition":"long_short",
        "Group":4,
        "Item":2,
        "Filler":"no",
        "Repeat":null,
        "math_question":"6 + 14 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":20
    },
    {
        "Subject":"The businessman",
        "Verb":"called",
        "PP1":"from the airport",
        "PP2":"about the meeting\nthat was busy",
        "Math":"31 + 39 = ?",
        "Answer1":70,
        "Answer2":71,
        "Prep1":"from",
        "Prep2":"about",
        "Transitivity":"intransitive",
        "ModifierPosition":"postnominal",
        "ModifierLen":"short",
        "Condition":"short_long",
        "Group":4,
        "Item":3,
        "Filler":"no",
        "Repeat":null,
        "math_question":"7 + 10 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":17
    },
    {
        "Subject":"The actress",
        "Verb":"competed",
        "PP1":"for the role",
        "PP2":"during the audition",
        "Math":"16 + 34 = ?",
        "Answer1":50,
        "Answer2":54,
        "Prep1":"for",
        "Prep2":"during",
        "Transitivity":"intransitive",
        "ModifierPosition":"none",
        "ModifierLen":"none",
        "Condition":"short_short",
        "Group":5,
        "Item":1,
        "Filler":"no",
        "Repeat":null,
        "math_question":"8 + 7 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":15
    },
    {
        "Subject":"The actress",
        "Verb":"competed",
        "PP1":"for the important\nand competitive role",
        "PP2":"during the auditon",
        "Math":"44 + 17 = ?",
        "Answer1":61,
        "Answer2":64,
        "Prep1":"for",
        "Prep2":"during",
        "Transitivity":"intransitive",
        "ModifierPosition":"prenominal",
        "ModifierLen":"medium",
        "Condition":"short_long",
        "Group":5,
        "Item":2,
        "Filler":"no",
        "Repeat":null,
        "math_question":"14 + 9 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":23
    },
    {
        "Subject":"The actress",
        "Verb":"competed",
        "PP1":"for the role",
        "PP2":"during the important\nand competitive\naudition",
        "Math":"52 + 18 = ?",
        "Answer1":70,
        "Answer2":72,
        "Prep1":"for",
        "Prep2":"during",
        "Transitivity":"intransitive",
        "ModifierPosition":"prenominal",
        "ModifierLen":"medium",
        "Condition":"long_short",
        "Group":5,
        "Item":3,
        "Filler":"no",
        "Repeat":null,
        "math_question":"10 + 9 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":19
    },
    {
        "Subject":"The girl",
        "Verb":"chatted",
        "PP1":"with her roommate",
        "PP2":"about the bathroom",
        "Math":"49 + 6 = ?",
        "Answer1":55,
        "Answer2":56,
        "Prep1":"with",
        "Prep2":"about",
        "Transitivity":"intransitive",
        "ModifierPosition":"none",
        "ModifierLen":"none",
        "Condition":"short_short",
        "Group":6,
        "Item":1,
        "Filler":"no",
        "Repeat":null,
        "math_question":"10 + 6 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":16
    },
    {
        "Subject":"The girl",
        "Verb":"chatted",
        "PP1":"with her messy and\ndisorganized\nroommate",
        "PP2":"about the bathroom",
        "Math":"47 + 78 = ?",
        "Answer1":125,
        "Answer2":115,
        "Prep1":"with",
        "Prep2":"about",
        "Transitivity":"intransitive",
        "ModifierPosition":"prenominal",
        "ModifierLen":"medium",
        "Condition":"short_long",
        "Group":6,
        "Item":2,
        "Filler":"no",
        "Repeat":null,
        "math_question":"13 + 13 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":26
    },
    {
        "Subject":"The girl",
        "Verb":"chatted",
        "PP1":"with her roommate",
        "PP2":"about the messy and\ndisorganized\nbathroom",
        "Math":"85 + 51 = ?",
        "Answer1":136,
        "Answer2":126,
        "Prep1":"with",
        "Prep2":"about",
        "Transitivity":"intransitive",
        "ModifierPosition":"prenominal",
        "ModifierLen":"medium",
        "Condition":"long_short",
        "Group":6,
        "Item":3,
        "Filler":"no",
        "Repeat":null,
        "math_question":"6 + 8 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":14
    },
    {
        "Subject":"The waiter",
        "Verb":"hurried",
        "PP1":"into the kitchen",
        "PP2":"with the tray",
        "Math":"12 + 60 = ?",
        "Answer1":72,
        "Answer2":70,
        "Prep1":"into",
        "Prep2":"with",
        "Transitivity":"intransitive",
        "ModifierPosition":"none",
        "ModifierLen":"none",
        "Condition":"short_short",
        "Group":7,
        "Item":1,
        "Filler":"no",
        "Repeat":null,
        "math_question":"11 + 15 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":26
    },
    {
        "Subject":"The waiter",
        "Verb":"hurried",
        "PP1":"into the kitchen\nthat was full of\ndishes",
        "PP2":"with the tray",
        "Math":"46 + 37 = ?",
        "Answer1":83,
        "Answer2":84,
        "Prep1":"into",
        "Prep2":"with",
        "Transitivity":"intransitive",
        "ModifierPosition":"postnominal",
        "ModifierLen":"medium",
        "Condition":"short_long",
        "Group":7,
        "Item":2,
        "Filler":"no",
        "Repeat":null,
        "math_question":"15 + 7 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":22
    },
    {
        "Subject":"The waiter",
        "Verb":"hurried",
        "PP1":"into the kitchen",
        "PP2":"with the tray that\nwas full of dishes",
        "Math":"94 + 23 = ?",
        "Answer1":117,
        "Answer2":127,
        "Prep1":"into",
        "Prep2":"with",
        "Transitivity":"intransitive",
        "ModifierPosition":"postnominal",
        "ModifierLen":"medium",
        "Condition":"long_short",
        "Group":7,
        "Item":3,
        "Filler":"no",
        "Repeat":null,
        "math_question":"11 + 7 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":18
    },
    {
        "Subject":"The client",
        "Verb":"spoke",
        "PP1":"with his lawyer",
        "PP2":"about the judge",
        "Math":"45 + 9 = ?",
        "Answer1":54,
        "Answer2":56,
        "Prep1":"with",
        "Prep2":"about",
        "Transitivity":"intransitive",
        "ModifierPosition":"none",
        "ModifierLen":"none",
        "Condition":"short_short",
        "Group":8,
        "Item":1,
        "Filler":"no",
        "Repeat":null,
        "math_question":"7 + 8 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":15
    },
    {
        "Subject":"The client",
        "Verb":"spoke",
        "PP1":"with his lawyer who\nseems to lack\nexperience",
        "PP2":"about the judge",
        "Math":"64 + 11 = ?",
        "Answer1":75,
        "Answer2":76,
        "Prep1":"with",
        "Prep2":"about",
        "Transitivity":"intransitive",
        "ModifierPosition":"postnominal",
        "ModifierLen":"medium",
        "Condition":"short_long",
        "Group":8,
        "Item":2,
        "Filler":"no",
        "Repeat":null,
        "math_question":"9 + 8 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":17
    },
    {
        "Subject":"The client",
        "Verb":"spoke",
        "PP1":"with his lawyer",
        "PP2":"about the judge who\nseems to lack\nexperience",
        "Math":"7 + 94 = ?",
        "Answer1":101,
        "Answer2":100,
        "Prep1":"with",
        "Prep2":"about",
        "Transitivity":"intransitive",
        "ModifierPosition":"postnominal",
        "ModifierLen":"medium",
        "Condition":"long_short",
        "Group":8,
        "Item":3,
        "Filler":"no",
        "Repeat":null,
        "math_question":"9 + 5 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":14
    },
    {
        "Subject":"The actress",
        "Verb":"danced",
        "PP1":"at the gala",
        "PP2":"in her heels",
        "Math":"15 + 19 = ?",
        "Answer1":34,
        "Answer2":33,
        "Prep1":"at",
        "Prep2":"in",
        "Transitivity":"intransitive",
        "ModifierPosition":"none",
        "ModifierLen":"none",
        "Condition":"short_short",
        "Group":9,
        "Item":1,
        "Filler":"no",
        "Repeat":null,
        "math_question":"15 + 8 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":23
    },
    {
        "Subject":"The actress",
        "Verb":"danced",
        "PP1":"at the fashionable\nbut slightly awkward\ngala",
        "PP2":"in her heels",
        "Math":"66 + 67 = ?",
        "Answer1":133,
        "Answer2":123,
        "Prep1":"at",
        "Prep2":"in",
        "Transitivity":"intransitive",
        "ModifierPosition":"prenominal",
        "ModifierLen":"long",
        "Condition":"short_long",
        "Group":9,
        "Item":2,
        "Filler":"no",
        "Repeat":null,
        "math_question":"13 + 9 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":22
    },
    {
        "Subject":"The actress",
        "Verb":"danced",
        "PP1":"at the gala",
        "PP2":"in her fashionable\nbut slightly awkward\nheels",
        "Math":"34 + 64 = ?",
        "Answer1":98,
        "Answer2":108,
        "Prep1":"at",
        "Prep2":"in",
        "Transitivity":"intransitive",
        "ModifierPosition":"prenominal",
        "ModifierLen":"long",
        "Condition":"long_short",
        "Group":9,
        "Item":3,
        "Filler":"no",
        "Repeat":null,
        "math_question":"5 + 9 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":14
    },
    {
        "Subject":"The student",
        "Verb":"listened",
        "PP1":"to a lecture",
        "PP2":"for three hours",
        "Math":"96 + 72 = ?",
        "Answer1":168,
        "Answer2":178,
        "Prep1":"to",
        "Prep2":"for",
        "Transitivity":"intransitive",
        "ModifierPosition":"none",
        "ModifierLen":"none",
        "Condition":"short_short",
        "Group":10,
        "Item":1,
        "Filler":"no",
        "Repeat":null,
        "math_question":"7 + 6 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":13
    },
    {
        "Subject":"The student",
        "Verb":"listened",
        "PP1":"to an extremely\nboring and tedius\nlecture",
        "PP2":"for three hours",
        "Math":"74 + 68 = ?",
        "Answer1":142,
        "Answer2":132,
        "Prep1":"to",
        "Prep2":"for",
        "Transitivity":"intransitive",
        "ModifierPosition":"prenominal",
        "ModifierLen":"long",
        "Condition":"short_long",
        "Group":10,
        "Item":2,
        "Filler":"no",
        "Repeat":null,
        "math_question":"13 + 15 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":28
    },
    {
        "Subject":"The student",
        "Verb":"listened",
        "PP1":"to a lecture",
        "PP2":"for an extremely\nboring and tedius\nthree hours",
        "Math":"21 + 50 = ?",
        "Answer1":71,
        "Answer2":61,
        "Prep1":"to",
        "Prep2":"for",
        "Transitivity":"intransitive",
        "ModifierPosition":"prenominal",
        "ModifierLen":"long",
        "Condition":"long_short",
        "Group":10,
        "Item":3,
        "Filler":"no",
        "Repeat":null,
        "math_question":"6 + 8 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":14
    },
    {
        "Subject":"The girl",
        "Verb":"vented",
        "PP1":"to her therapist",
        "PP2":"about her boyfriend",
        "Math":"42 + 35 = ?",
        "Answer1":77,
        "Answer2":87,
        "Prep1":"to",
        "Prep2":"about",
        "Transitivity":"intransitive",
        "ModifierPosition":"none",
        "ModifierLen":"none",
        "Condition":"short_short",
        "Group":11,
        "Item":1,
        "Filler":"no",
        "Repeat":null,
        "math_question":"7 + 12 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":19
    },
    {
        "Subject":"The girl",
        "Verb":"vented",
        "PP1":"to her therapist who\nshe has been seeing\nfor some time",
        "PP2":"about her boyfriend",
        "Math":"30 + 5 = ?",
        "Answer1":35,
        "Answer2":36,
        "Prep1":"to",
        "Prep2":"about",
        "Transitivity":"intransitive",
        "ModifierPosition":"postnominal",
        "ModifierLen":"long",
        "Condition":"short_long",
        "Group":11,
        "Item":2,
        "Filler":"no",
        "Repeat":null,
        "math_question":"6 + 9 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":15
    },
    {
        "Subject":"The girl",
        "Verb":"vented",
        "PP1":"to her therapist",
        "PP2":"about her boyfriend\nwho she has been\nseeing for some time",
        "Math":"91 + 89 = ?",
        "Answer1":180,
        "Answer2":178,
        "Prep1":"to",
        "Prep2":"about",
        "Transitivity":"intransitive",
        "ModifierPosition":"postnominal",
        "ModifierLen":"long",
        "Condition":"long_short",
        "Group":11,
        "Item":3,
        "Filler":"no",
        "Repeat":null,
        "math_question":"14 + 9 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":23
    },
    {
        "Subject":"The lady",
        "Verb":"heard",
        "PP1":"from her friend",
        "PP2":"about the baby",
        "Math":"27 + 56 = ?",
        "Answer1":83,
        "Answer2":93,
        "Prep1":"from",
        "Prep2":"about",
        "Transitivity":"intransitive",
        "ModifierPosition":"none",
        "ModifierLen":"none",
        "Condition":"short_short",
        "Group":12,
        "Item":1,
        "Filler":"no",
        "Repeat":null,
        "math_question":"11 + 6 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":17
    },
    {
        "Subject":"The lady",
        "Verb":"heard",
        "PP1":"from her friend who\nwas just discharged\nfrom the hospital",
        "PP2":"nan",
        "Math":"101 + 53 = ?",
        "Answer1":154,
        "Answer2":153,
        "Prep1":"from",
        "Prep2":"about",
        "Transitivity":"intransitive",
        "ModifierPosition":"postnominal",
        "ModifierLen":"long",
        "Condition":"short_long",
        "Group":12,
        "Item":2,
        "Filler":"no",
        "Repeat":null,
        "math_question":"14 + 7 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":21
    },
    {
        "Subject":"The lady",
        "Verb":"heard",
        "PP1":"from her friend",
        "PP2":"about the baby who\nwas just discharged\nfrom the hospital",
        "Math":"37 + 2 = ?",
        "Answer1":39,
        "Answer2":40,
        "Prep1":"from",
        "Prep2":"about",
        "Transitivity":"intransitive",
        "ModifierPosition":"postnominal",
        "ModifierLen":"long",
        "Condition":"long_short",
        "Group":12,
        "Item":3,
        "Filler":"no",
        "Repeat":null,
        "math_question":"8 + 6 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":14
    },
    {
        "Subject":"The child",
        "Verb":"played the piano",
        "PP1":"for the director",
        "PP2":"during the audition",
        "Math":"24 + 55 = ?",
        "Answer1":79,
        "Answer2":80,
        "Prep1":"for",
        "Prep2":"during",
        "Transitivity":"transitive",
        "ModifierPosition":"none",
        "ModifierLen":"none",
        "Condition":"short_short",
        "Group":13,
        "Item":1,
        "Filler":"no",
        "Repeat":null,
        "math_question":"14 + 7 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":21
    },
    {
        "Subject":"The child",
        "Verb":"played the piano",
        "PP1":"for the very\ndemanding director",
        "PP2":"during the audition",
        "Math":"70 + 86 = ?",
        "Answer1":156,
        "Answer2":150,
        "Prep1":"for",
        "Prep2":"during",
        "Transitivity":"transitive",
        "ModifierPosition":"prenominal",
        "ModifierLen":"short",
        "Condition":"short_long",
        "Group":13,
        "Item":2,
        "Filler":"no",
        "Repeat":null,
        "math_question":"6 + 8 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":14
    },
    {
        "Subject":"The child",
        "Verb":"played the piano",
        "PP1":"for the director",
        "PP2":"during the very\ndemanding audition",
        "Math":"77 + 55 = ?",
        "Answer1":132,
        "Answer2":122,
        "Prep1":"for",
        "Prep2":"during",
        "Transitivity":"transitive",
        "ModifierPosition":"prenominal",
        "ModifierLen":"short",
        "Condition":"long_short",
        "Group":13,
        "Item":3,
        "Filler":"no",
        "Repeat":null,
        "math_question":"6 + 5 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":11
    },
    {
        "Subject":"The robber",
        "Verb":"made an escape",
        "PP1":"from the\nneighborhood",
        "PP2":"with the jewelry",
        "Math":"19 + 63 = ?",
        "Answer1":82,
        "Answer2":84,
        "Prep1":"from",
        "Prep2":"with",
        "Transitivity":"transitive",
        "ModifierPosition":"none",
        "ModifierLen":"none",
        "Condition":"short_short",
        "Group":14,
        "Item":1,
        "Filler":"no",
        "Repeat":null,
        "math_question":"9 + 5 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":14
    },
    {
        "Subject":"The robber",
        "Verb":"made an escape",
        "PP1":"from the extremely\nexpensive\nneighborhood",
        "PP2":"with the jewelry",
        "Math":"87 + 29 = ?",
        "Answer1":116,
        "Answer2":113,
        "Prep1":"from",
        "Prep2":"with",
        "Transitivity":"transitive",
        "ModifierPosition":"prenominal",
        "ModifierLen":"short",
        "Condition":"short_long",
        "Group":14,
        "Item":2,
        "Filler":"no",
        "Repeat":null,
        "math_question":"7 + 5 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":12
    },
    {
        "Subject":"The robber",
        "Verb":"made an escape",
        "PP1":"from the\nneighborhood",
        "PP2":"with the extremely\nexpensive jewelry",
        "Math":"1 + 103 = ?",
        "Answer1":104,
        "Answer2":105,
        "Prep1":"from",
        "Prep2":"with",
        "Transitivity":"transitive",
        "ModifierPosition":"prenominal",
        "ModifierLen":"short",
        "Condition":"long_short",
        "Group":14,
        "Item":3,
        "Filler":"no",
        "Repeat":null,
        "math_question":"5 + 12 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":17
    },
    {
        "Subject":"The barista",
        "Verb":"made coffee",
        "PP1":"from the whole beans",
        "PP2":"with the espresso\nmachine",
        "Math":"45 + 84 = ?",
        "Answer1":129,
        "Answer2":130,
        "Prep1":"for",
        "Prep2":"during",
        "Transitivity":"transitive",
        "ModifierPosition":"none",
        "ModifierLen":"none",
        "Condition":"short_short",
        "Group":15,
        "Item":1,
        "Filler":"no",
        "Repeat":null,
        "math_question":"12 + 13 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":25
    },
    {
        "Subject":"The barista",
        "Verb":"made coffee",
        "PP1":"from the whole beans\nthat he just\npurchased",
        "PP2":"with the espresso\nmachine",
        "Math":"15 + 48 = ?",
        "Answer1":63,
        "Answer2":53,
        "Prep1":"for",
        "Prep2":"during",
        "Transitivity":"transitive",
        "ModifierPosition":"postnominal",
        "ModifierLen":"short",
        "Condition":"short_long",
        "Group":15,
        "Item":2,
        "Filler":"no",
        "Repeat":null,
        "math_question":"10 + 13 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":23
    },
    {
        "Subject":"The barista",
        "Verb":"made coffee",
        "PP1":"from the whole beans",
        "PP2":"with the espresso\nmachine that he just\npurchased",
        "Math":"65 + 54 = ?",
        "Answer1":119,
        "Answer2":122,
        "Prep1":"for",
        "Prep2":"during",
        "Transitivity":"transitive",
        "ModifierPosition":"postnominal",
        "ModifierLen":"short",
        "Condition":"long_short",
        "Group":15,
        "Item":3,
        "Filler":"no",
        "Repeat":null,
        "math_question":"13 + 14 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":27
    },
    {
        "Subject":"The tourist",
        "Verb":"read a book",
        "PP1":"on the bed",
        "PP2":"throughout the night",
        "Math":"43 + 52 = ?",
        "Answer1":95,
        "Answer2":85,
        "Prep1":"on",
        "Prep2":"throughout",
        "Transitivity":"transitive",
        "ModifierPosition":"none",
        "ModifierLen":"none",
        "Condition":"short_short",
        "Group":16,
        "Item":1,
        "Filler":"no",
        "Repeat":null,
        "math_question":"10 + 6 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":16
    },
    {
        "Subject":"The tourist",
        "Verb":"read a book",
        "PP1":"on the bed that is\ncozy",
        "PP2":"throughout the night",
        "Math":"69 + 97 = ?",
        "Answer1":166,
        "Answer2":156,
        "Prep1":"on",
        "Prep2":"throughout",
        "Transitivity":"transitive",
        "ModifierPosition":"postnominal",
        "ModifierLen":"short",
        "Condition":"short_long",
        "Group":16,
        "Item":2,
        "Filler":"no",
        "Repeat":null,
        "math_question":"11 + 15 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":26
    },
    {
        "Subject":"The tourist",
        "Verb":"read a book",
        "PP1":"on the bed",
        "PP2":"throughout the night\nthat is cozy",
        "Math":"56 + 91 = ?",
        "Answer1":147,
        "Answer2":156,
        "Prep1":"on",
        "Prep2":"throughout",
        "Transitivity":"transitive",
        "ModifierPosition":"postnominal",
        "ModifierLen":"short",
        "Condition":"long_short",
        "Group":16,
        "Item":3,
        "Filler":"no",
        "Repeat":null,
        "math_question":"9 + 8 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":17
    },
    {
        "Subject":"The dad",
        "Verb":"bought a gift",
        "PP1":"for his daughter",
        "PP2":"in the airport",
        "Math":"65 + 30 = ?",
        "Answer1":95,
        "Answer2":85,
        "Prep1":"for",
        "Prep2":"in",
        "Transitivity":"transitive",
        "ModifierPosition":"none",
        "ModifierLen":"none",
        "Condition":"short_short",
        "Group":17,
        "Item":1,
        "Filler":"no",
        "Repeat":null,
        "math_question":"5 + 9 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":14
    },
    {
        "Subject":"The dad",
        "Verb":"bought a gift",
        "PP1":"for his calm and\nquiet daughter",
        "PP2":"in the airport",
        "Math":"102 + 79 = ?",
        "Answer1":181,
        "Answer2":180,
        "Prep1":"for",
        "Prep2":"in",
        "Transitivity":"transitive",
        "ModifierPosition":"prenominal",
        "ModifierLen":"medium",
        "Condition":"short_long",
        "Group":17,
        "Item":2,
        "Filler":"no",
        "Repeat":null,
        "math_question":"5 + 14 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":19
    },
    {
        "Subject":"The dad",
        "Verb":"bought a gift",
        "PP1":"for his daughter",
        "PP2":"in the calm and\nquiet airport",
        "Math":"17 + 41 = ?",
        "Answer1":58,
        "Answer2":47,
        "Prep1":"for",
        "Prep2":"in",
        "Transitivity":"transitive",
        "ModifierPosition":"prenominal",
        "ModifierLen":"medium",
        "Condition":"long_short",
        "Group":17,
        "Item":3,
        "Filler":"no",
        "Repeat":null,
        "math_question":"7 + 12 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":19
    },
    {
        "Subject":"The student",
        "Verb":"sent an email",
        "PP1":"to his teacher",
        "PP2":"about the homework",
        "Math":"41 + 31 = ?",
        "Answer1":72,
        "Answer2":62,
        "Prep1":"to",
        "Prep2":"about",
        "Transitivity":"transitive",
        "ModifierPosition":"none",
        "ModifierLen":"none",
        "Condition":"short_short",
        "Group":18,
        "Item":1,
        "Filler":"no",
        "Repeat":null,
        "math_question":"8 + 5 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":13
    },
    {
        "Subject":"The student",
        "Verb":"sent an email",
        "PP1":"to his difficult and\nconfusing teacher",
        "PP2":"about the homework",
        "Math":"68 + 36 = ?",
        "Answer1":104,
        "Answer2":94,
        "Prep1":"to",
        "Prep2":"about",
        "Transitivity":"transitive",
        "ModifierPosition":"prenominal",
        "ModifierLen":"medium",
        "Condition":"short_long",
        "Group":18,
        "Item":2,
        "Filler":"no",
        "Repeat":null,
        "math_question":"5 + 7 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":12
    },
    {
        "Subject":"The student",
        "Verb":"sent an email",
        "PP1":"to his teacher",
        "PP2":"about the difficult\nand confusing\nhomework",
        "Math":"24 + 32 = ?",
        "Answer1":56,
        "Answer2":55,
        "Prep1":"to",
        "Prep2":"about",
        "Transitivity":"transitive",
        "ModifierPosition":"prenominal",
        "ModifierLen":"medium",
        "Condition":"long_short",
        "Group":18,
        "Item":3,
        "Filler":"no",
        "Repeat":null,
        "math_question":"9 + 13 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":22
    },
    {
        "Subject":"The robber",
        "Verb":"dug a tunnel",
        "PP1":"into the vault",
        "PP2":"with his tools",
        "Math":"17 + 18 = ?",
        "Answer1":35,
        "Answer2":36,
        "Prep1":"into",
        "Prep2":"with",
        "Transitivity":"transitive",
        "ModifierPosition":"none",
        "ModifierLen":"none",
        "Condition":"short_short",
        "Group":19,
        "Item":1,
        "Filler":"no",
        "Repeat":null,
        "math_question":"6 + 13 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":19
    },
    {
        "Subject":"The robber",
        "Verb":"dug a tunnel",
        "PP1":"into the vault that\nwas very high-tech",
        "PP2":"with his tools",
        "Math":"32 + 5 = ?",
        "Answer1":37,
        "Answer2":48,
        "Prep1":"into",
        "Prep2":"with",
        "Transitivity":"transitive",
        "ModifierPosition":"postnominal",
        "ModifierLen":"medium",
        "Condition":"short_long",
        "Group":19,
        "Item":2,
        "Filler":"no",
        "Repeat":null,
        "math_question":"8 + 12 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":20
    },
    {
        "Subject":"The robber",
        "Verb":"dug a tunnel",
        "PP1":"into the vault",
        "PP2":"with his tools that\nwere very high-tech",
        "Math":"50 + 57 = ?",
        "Answer1":107,
        "Answer2":117,
        "Prep1":"into",
        "Prep2":"with",
        "Transitivity":"transitive",
        "ModifierPosition":"postnominal",
        "ModifierLen":"medium",
        "Condition":"long_short",
        "Group":19,
        "Item":3,
        "Filler":"no",
        "Repeat":null,
        "math_question":"8 + 13 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":21
    },
    {
        "Subject":"The boy",
        "Verb":"rode the bike",
        "PP1":"into the pool",
        "PP2":"with the helmet",
        "Math":"22 + 63 = ?",
        "Answer1":85,
        "Answer2":83,
        "Prep1":"into",
        "Prep2":"with",
        "Transitivity":"transitive",
        "ModifierPosition":"none",
        "ModifierLen":"none",
        "Condition":"short_short",
        "Group":20,
        "Item":1,
        "Filler":"no",
        "Repeat":null,
        "math_question":"8 + 10 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":18
    },
    {
        "Subject":"The boy",
        "Verb":"rode the bike",
        "PP1":"into the pool that\nis near the garage",
        "PP2":"with the helmet",
        "Math":"38 + 3 = ?",
        "Answer1":41,
        "Answer2":39,
        "Prep1":"into",
        "Prep2":"with",
        "Transitivity":"transitive",
        "ModifierPosition":"postnominal",
        "ModifierLen":"medium",
        "Condition":"short_long",
        "Group":20,
        "Item":2,
        "Filler":"no",
        "Repeat":null,
        "math_question":"10 + 14 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":24
    },
    {
        "Subject":"The boy",
        "Verb":"rode the bike",
        "PP1":"into the pool",
        "PP2":"with the helmet that\nis near the garage",
        "Math":"42 + 7 = ?",
        "Answer1":49,
        "Answer2":50,
        "Prep1":"into",
        "Prep2":"with",
        "Transitivity":"transitive",
        "ModifierPosition":"postnominal",
        "ModifierLen":"medium",
        "Condition":"long_short",
        "Group":20,
        "Item":3,
        "Filler":"no",
        "Repeat":null,
        "math_question":"7 + 6 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":13
    },
    {
        "Subject":"The attorney",
        "Verb":"made a scene",
        "PP1":"over the ruling",
        "PP2":"after the hearing",
        "Math":"77 + 61 = ?",
        "Answer1":138,
        "Answer2":137,
        "Prep1":"over",
        "Prep2":"after",
        "Transitivity":"transitive",
        "ModifierPosition":"none",
        "ModifierLen":"none",
        "Condition":"short_short",
        "Group":21,
        "Item":1,
        "Filler":"no",
        "Repeat":null,
        "math_question":"9 + 6 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":15
    },
    {
        "Subject":"The attorney",
        "Verb":"made a scene",
        "PP1":"over the quite\nunjust and delayed\nruling",
        "PP2":"after the hearing",
        "Math":"35 + 28 = ?",
        "Answer1":63,
        "Answer2":62,
        "Prep1":"over",
        "Prep2":"after",
        "Transitivity":"transitive",
        "ModifierPosition":"prenominal",
        "ModifierLen":"long",
        "Condition":"short_long",
        "Group":21,
        "Item":2,
        "Filler":"no",
        "Repeat":null,
        "math_question":"11 + 12 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":23
    },
    {
        "Subject":"The attorney",
        "Verb":"made a scene",
        "PP1":"over the ruling",
        "PP2":"after the quite\nunjust and delayed\nhearing",
        "Math":"78 + 13 = ?",
        "Answer1":91,
        "Answer2":93,
        "Prep1":"over",
        "Prep2":"after",
        "Transitivity":"transitive",
        "ModifierPosition":"prenominal",
        "ModifierLen":"long",
        "Condition":"long_short",
        "Group":21,
        "Item":3,
        "Filler":"no",
        "Repeat":null,
        "math_question":"6 + 8 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":14
    },
    {
        "Subject":"The performer",
        "Verb":"sang a song",
        "PP1":"to the crowd",
        "PP2":"before the game",
        "Math":"29 + 58 = ?",
        "Answer1":87,
        "Answer2":78,
        "Prep1":"to",
        "Prep2":"before",
        "Transitivity":"transitive",
        "ModifierPosition":"none",
        "ModifierLen":"none",
        "Condition":"short_short",
        "Group":22,
        "Item":1,
        "Filler":"no",
        "Repeat":null,
        "math_question":"10 + 10 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":20
    },
    {
        "Subject":"The performer",
        "Verb":"sang a song",
        "PP1":"to the beautiful\nlively and exciting\ncrowd",
        "PP2":"before the game",
        "Math":"16 + 58 = ?",
        "Answer1":74,
        "Answer2":76,
        "Prep1":"to",
        "Prep2":"before",
        "Transitivity":"transitive",
        "ModifierPosition":"prenominal",
        "ModifierLen":"long",
        "Condition":"short_long",
        "Group":22,
        "Item":2,
        "Filler":"no",
        "Repeat":null,
        "math_question":"9 + 13 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":22
    },
    {
        "Subject":"The performer",
        "Verb":"sang a song",
        "PP1":"to the crowd",
        "PP2":"before the beaitufl\nlively and exciting\ngame",
        "Math":"37 + 34 = ?",
        "Answer1":71,
        "Answer2":63,
        "Prep1":"to",
        "Prep2":"before",
        "Transitivity":"transitive",
        "ModifierPosition":"prenominal",
        "ModifierLen":"long",
        "Condition":"long_short",
        "Group":22,
        "Item":3,
        "Filler":"no",
        "Repeat":null,
        "math_question":"15 + 9 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":24
    },
    {
        "Subject":"The chef",
        "Verb":"cooked dinner",
        "PP1":"with the recipe",
        "PP2":"for the host",
        "Math":"4 + 59 = ?",
        "Answer1":63,
        "Answer2":65,
        "Prep1":"with",
        "Prep2":"for",
        "Transitivity":"transitive",
        "ModifierPosition":"none",
        "ModifierLen":"none",
        "Condition":"short_short",
        "Group":23,
        "Item":1,
        "Filler":"no",
        "Repeat":null,
        "math_question":"7 + 7 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":14
    },
    {
        "Subject":"The chef",
        "Verb":"cooked dinner",
        "PP1":"with the recipe that\nhas gotten popular\nover the years",
        "PP2":"for the host",
        "Math":"25 + 81 = ?",
        "Answer1":106,
        "Answer2":105,
        "Prep1":"with",
        "Prep2":"for",
        "Transitivity":"transitive",
        "ModifierPosition":"postnominal",
        "ModifierLen":"long",
        "Condition":"short_long",
        "Group":23,
        "Item":2,
        "Filler":"no",
        "Repeat":null,
        "math_question":"15 + 7 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":22
    },
    {
        "Subject":"The chef",
        "Verb":"cooked dinner",
        "PP1":"with the recipe",
        "PP2":"for the host that\nhas gotten popular\nover the years",
        "Math":"78 + 109 = ?",
        "Answer1":187,
        "Answer2":189,
        "Prep1":"with",
        "Prep2":"for",
        "Transitivity":"transitive",
        "ModifierPosition":"postnominal",
        "ModifierLen":"long",
        "Condition":"long_short",
        "Group":23,
        "Item":3,
        "Filler":"no",
        "Repeat":null,
        "math_question":"11 + 14 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":25
    },
    {
        "Subject":"The couple",
        "Verb":"moved the furnitures",
        "PP1":"with the truck",
        "PP2":"to the apartment",
        "Math":"14 + 28 = ?",
        "Answer1":42,
        "Answer2":44,
        "Prep1":"with",
        "Prep2":"to",
        "Transitivity":"transitive",
        "ModifierPosition":"none",
        "ModifierLen":"none",
        "Condition":"short_short",
        "Group":24,
        "Item":1,
        "Filler":"no",
        "Repeat":null,
        "math_question":"10 + 12 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":22
    },
    {
        "Subject":"The couple",
        "Verb":"moved the furnitures",
        "PP1":"with the truck that\nthey just bought\nlast week",
        "PP2":"to the apartment",
        "Math":"35 + 77 = ?",
        "Answer1":112,
        "Answer2":102,
        "Prep1":"with",
        "Prep2":"to",
        "Transitivity":"transitive",
        "ModifierPosition":"postnominal",
        "ModifierLen":"long",
        "Condition":"short_long",
        "Group":24,
        "Item":2,
        "Filler":"no",
        "Repeat":null,
        "math_question":"6 + 7 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":13
    },
    {
        "Subject":"The couple",
        "Verb":"moved the furnitures",
        "PP1":"with the truck",
        "PP2":"to the apartment\nthat they just\nbought last week",
        "Math":"67 + 16 = ?",
        "Answer1":83,
        "Answer2":81,
        "Prep1":"with",
        "Prep2":"to",
        "Transitivity":"transitive",
        "ModifierPosition":"postnominal",
        "ModifierLen":"long",
        "Condition":"long_short",
        "Group":24,
        "Item":3,
        "Filler":"no",
        "Repeat":null,
        "math_question":"9 + 11 = ?",
        "math_correct_answer":20
    }
]